What's up, Rashad? Reporting live from
Rashad.
>> Thank you, Rashad. Peace and
Pan-Africanism.
>> [laughter]
>> Hey, Rashad. What up?
>> Hey, Rashad.
>> All right, Amanda Seales was left off
the the Insecure tour. This is from last
week, but I never got to react to it.
So, I'm going to react to it right now.
>> I can't friend At first, I was like,
"Y'all are taking this Insecure thing
too far." Like, it's it I mean, it's my
experience. Otherwise, it felt like,
"What's the point?" However, seeing the
visceral response from fans brought
seeing to when I took the Black Popular
Culture class that Professor Donna Davis
taught at Sunni Purchase, and she really
drilled home that art for black folks,
particularly in the United States, is
not simply just about entertainment. It
is political because it is our
representation and in our own voice.
That is something that we rarely get.
So, our characters and our stories are
not simply just meant to entertain. They
are literally meant as proof of life.
And so, that made me say, "Okay, I need
to talk about this further, but in a
greater context."
Let's talk about
the difference between
lack and abundance.
A lack conversation
is, "Why would Amanda expect to be
invited to the Insecure reunion?"
An abundance conversation is, "Why were
amends not made so that Amanda would be
present at the Insecure reunion?"
Ultimately, a reunion tour for a TV show
would be all about pleasing the fans of
that show. That's the goal. And I would
suggest that the fans of a show want to
see the characters that they have
aligned with. There are many people who
have said they didn't give a damn about
Tiffany. However, I know, because I
experience it on a regular basis, there
are so many women in particular, mothers
in particular, who very much aligned
with Tiffany's um, journey through
postpartum depression and really
connected with me like in person to say
thank you for portraying that in such a
realistic way.
Which is also why, you know, the
performance of stories on speak on
screen is so imperative because people,
humans, we need to be seen. On a larger
scale,
I'm always thinking of how do I show up
in abundance versus lack. I didn't
always think that way. However, as I
have grown, particularly in the last 3
years, spiritually, intellectually,
communally, that has definitely been a
shift. And the difference between lack
and abundance is important
because lack is patriarchal and it deals
with the failure to see growth, to see
expansion
on a communal level.
So,
uh, abundance, on the other hand, is
matriarchal and is about restoration.
And so, the difference is imperative to
how we even view our role in resistance
on a much bigger scale.
While I have you, if you'd like to hear
me talk about things on a abundance
level, you can check out my new radio
show on Tavis Smiley's KBLA Talk 1580.
I'll be there every Friday with the
Summer of Seals from 12:00 to 2:00 p.m.
Pacific and 4:00 to 6:00 p.m. Pacific.
And you can check me out by downloading
the KBLA Talk Radio app or listening on
YouTube.
Hope to see you there or hear you there,
I should say, where we can talk about
abundance and how to get out of the lack
state that this capitalist, imperialist
empire has got us in.
>> Um, support Amanda Seales. Listen to her
radio show.
Uh,
because we are using Amanda Seales for
content right now.
She pretty much said of that just to say
like
it was either they didn't invite her to
the reunion
or they invited her to the reunion and
she said, "I don't like y'all."
"Why don't y'all apologize for bullying
me 10 years ago before I do this 10-year
anniversary thing?"
It was either one.
But it's kind of funny like how she just
talked like 3 minutes around that point.
>> [laughter]
[snorts]
>> One person from Insecure, aside from
Issa, spoke negatively about me.
He did so because I said I was not
interested in taking pictures together
at an event when we were not actually
acquainted. He later defended his
brother abusing
Oh, wow. Okay.
I think after your interview on Club
Shay Shay, Issa's for you all. For some
reason many of you think that is an
acceptable response. It is not. After
Shay Shay, she should have reached out
to apologize.
Hm.
I mean, you did say you ain't fool with
them folks.
It really isn't difficult to understand
that this job is it This is a job, is
it?
She sound like she don't want to be
there.
Genuine friendship and encouragement and
sisterhood, that's what drew so many of
us in. Everything happening now feels
counterproductive to the message of the
show originally set for because they are
fake.
All caps.
And come on, Amanda, come on.
Let's not play you are confrontational
along with valid confrontational factual
points of views. Miss Hill's on an
unscripted tour, baby. How much wood
could a woodchuck chuck if a woodchuck
chuck wood? When have you ever seen me
be confrontational and in the wrong.
Wait.
Amanda Seales. Amanda Seales be so for
real. I'll wait.
>> [snorts]
>> Amanda Seales be so for real. Your whole
brand is being confrontational, bro. You
think we all just lying on you? You
think the world just hate Amanda Seales?
Is Amanda Seales versus the world?
Be so for real, Amanda Seales. A fact is
information with objective reality, but
the truth reveals the why. The fact is
uh they wrongly excluded Amanda, but
they will ever but will they ever reveal
the truth as to why? Exactly. I just had
to point out the irony of them excluding
the only character in the Insecure
universe who always sold the truth. Life
imitating art, perhaps. And as she said,
right on the mark. Right on the mark.
But she said, "When have I ever been
honest and confrontational?"
Um [snorts]
one of the last memorable characters
that I could have done without, nasty
bougie light skin who was feeling it and
probably off camera, too. A lot of I'm
sorry, Amanda. I love your intelligence,
so Issa created the character accusing
me of being a nasty bougie light skin
with literally nothing to show for the
behavior says way more
uh about you than me.
I just want to know if you were ever
invited or if you would you have really
gone? If accountability were taken and
genuine apologies sent, then yes, of
course. That means she would she wasn't.
That that means she was invited. And she
said no. Because they didn't apologize
to her for her and her feelings 10 years
ago. That's what that means.
It's kind of annoying that that she
didn't just answer.
One person Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah,
okay. Yeah. Uh
I'm not arguing with it. Different
strokes for different folks. Different
strokes for different folks.
Still bad, though. Ain't going to lie.
Uh what is this? Trimmers pliers.
>> Um
>> [clears throat]
>> any obstacle, any depression, any any
sadness, anything that they
>> They they got uh
>> What's up, Rashad? Reporting live from
Rashad's
>> Thank you, Rashad.
>> Peace and Pan-Africanism.
>> Hello. John Bobby
>> Hey, man. What's up?
>> Turn the news
>> [laughter]
>> Hey, Rashad. What up?
>> Hey, Rashad.